<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Johnny Niu&#39;s Dev Space</title>
    <link>http://johnnyniu.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Johnny Niu&#39;s Dev Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 01:07:39 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://johnnyniu.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using different web frameworks to create a simple web app</title>
      <link>http://johnnyniu.com/post/taste-different-web-frameworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 01:07:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://johnnyniu.com/post/taste-different-web-frameworks/</guid>
      <description>Using different web frameworks to create a simple web app This is a trivial project, which is using some popular web mvc frameworks to create a dummy web app. Through this project I try to taste lavours of different flanguages and frameworks.
These language and framework includes:
Java+ Springboot + Hibernate + themyleaf Python + flask + sqlalchemy + jinja2 Ruby + Sinatra Golang Nodejs Continuing&amp;hellip;  The source code is here: repo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>what is proxy and reverse proxy</title>
      <link>http://johnnyniu.com/post/what-is-proxy-and-reverse-proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 01:07:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://johnnyniu.com/post/what-is-proxy-and-reverse-proxy/</guid>
      <description>What is proxy and reverse proxy What is Proxy Proxy is a dedicated server between client and server, act as an intermediary when user request a service from the server.
When user makes a request to the server via proxy, proxy will request server on user’s behalf using its own IP address, and then forward server’s response to user.
The purpose of using proxy server in Enterprise includes:
- Proxy can act as administrative control(whitelist/blacklist) - Proxy can act as a gateway which protect from malicious traffic - Proxy can cache the content for all users, which can improve user response time - Monitor and log traffic  Proxy can also be used for personal purpose, which: - Enables user anonymous surfing and privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>